(Penny:)Raj, wait.
(Penny:)Thank you for being my friend.
(Sheldon:)- Penny.
- Mm-hm.
(Raj:)It's getting beautiful again.
(Sheldon:)All right. This is a Google Earth view
of the field of battle.
(Sheldon:)Whenever you're ready, AT&T.
(Sheldon:)Okay, here we go. This is us, here.
(Sheldon:)To the south is Professor Loomis
and the Geology Department.
(Sheldon:)According to their Twitter feed,
they're out of sunblock...
(Sheldon:)...which means they'll have
to hug the tree line or risk melanoma.
(Sheldon:)That's our edge. All we have to do
is move quickly over this ridge.
(Sheldon:)The rock-worshipping, pasty-faced
bastards won't know what hit them.
(Sheldon:)Let's move out.
(Leonard:)Hang on, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)How could you not tell me
your sister was moving back to lndia?